(Man:)You know, if you ask nicely, they'll
let you visit the engine room.
(Sheldon:)I never want this day to end.
(Amy:)It's feeling like it never will.
(Amy:)Come on.
(Man:)Hey, did I tell you what
happened to me at UPS?
(Raj:)As if Valentine's Day wasn't bad
enough, you try to kill my dog?!
(Raj:)And with cheap chocolate, no less?
(Penny:)It wasn't cheap.
It was free.
(Leonard:)We're really sorry.
It was an accident.
(Penny:)Yeah, we weren't even out
of the room that long.
(Leonard:)No, come on. It was a while.
(Leonard:)It was a while.
-Is Cinnamon gonna be OK?
-She's responding well.
(Vet:)We just want to keep her
a little longer for observation.
All right. Would it be OK
for me to see her?
(Raj:)We're usually in bed by now,
and I want her to know that I'm here.
(Raj:)Yes, we sleep together,
and sometimes we spoon.
It's OK. I sleep with my dog, too.